TU-AN NGUYEN

+1-714-878-6337 | Fullerton, CA 92831 | t.nhunhu.ng@gmail.com | tu-annguyen.me | linkedin.com/in/tu-annguyen

SUMMARY

Recent graduate from the University of California, Santa Cruz with a focus on full stack web development. 7 years of graphic and interface design experience specializing in websites and marketing materials using the Adobe suite, Figma, and Wordpress. Looking to expand my technical skill set with a strong fundamental knowledge in visual design.

EXPERIENCE

Web/Graphics Specialist

Nov. 2019 - Jun. 2023

UC Santa Cruz Genomics Institute

Santa Cruz, CA, USA

- Use the Google G Suite, Divi for WordPress, and other content management systems along with knowledge of HTML/CSS and JavaScript to design and maintain team, publication, and news pages for 8+ websites
- · Leverage news and event content to drive traffic, increase reach, and raise awareness to websites
- Design flyers, posters, and other promotional and graphic materials

User Interface & Experience Intern

Oct. 2022 - Dec. 2022

Seoul, KOR

ACTIBrain Bio

- Designed and presented the user interface and experience of a "Braincare" program using Figma and Canva
- Conceptualized a modular game with 10+ hours of content that incorporates meditative exercise aimed for adults aged 40-60 to help prevent neurological diseases such as dementia, Parkinson's, and Alzheimer's
- Researched over 30 articles on the preventative benefits of alternative forms of meditative exercise such as Tai Chi in regards to neurological diseases

Marketing Web & Graphics Designer

Aug. 2019 - Feb. 2020

Union of Vietnamese Student Associations SoCal

Westminster, CA, USA

- · Updated event info, graphic assets, and sponsorships on the Tet Festival website using WordPress
- · Designed flyers, banners, and other marketing visuals by coordinating with leads and other designers

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: Java, Python, C/C++, SQL, JavaScript, HTML/CSS

Frameworks: React.js, Vue.js, Tailwind, Bulma, Bootstrap, WordPress

Developer Tools: Git, Google Cloud Platform, VS Code, Unix

Design Tools: Adobe Illustrator & Photoshop, Figma

EDUCATION

University of California, Santa Cruz

Sep. 2019 – Jun. 2023

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Santa Cruz, CA, USA

PROJECTS

Genrefy | *TailwindCSS*, *ReactJS* | genrefy

2023

- Front-end web application for searching songs' genres through the Spotify Web API
- · Built a reactive Spotify song search component using ReactJS and designed using TailwindCSS
- Calls the Spotify Web API with the Axios HTTP library to fetch song and artist data. Computed and visually designed collected data

Collaborative Planner | HTML/CSS, Bulma, Vue.js | collaborative-planner

2023

- Full-stack web application for managing tasks with collaborative features on a calendar with multiple views
- Implemented a majority of the database structure with py4web and front-end reactive elements with Vue.js

Troy High School Virtual Tour | HTML/CSS, Javascript | ths-virtual-tour

2018

- · Virtual campus tour of Troy High School with an emphasis on their Troy Tech program
- Constructed navigation and tour interface using HTML. Used CSS to create a responsive design. Implemented slideshow navigation and image/blurb toggles with vanilla Javascript